wefunder.com 2016-04-22

# Invest in Startups You Love - Wefunder

### We have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: (Note, this document is based upon the [Automattic Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and is licensed under a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/images/public/somerights20) license. This means you're more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use. Just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you!)

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please [contact us](mailto:%74%65%61%6d@%77%65%66%75%6e%64%65%72.%63%6f%6d)!

Wefunder operates several websites including [wefunder.com](http://www.wefunder.com/) and [blog.wefunder.com](http://blog.wefunder.com/). It is Wefunder’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Wefunder collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Wefunder's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Wefunder's visitors use its website. From time to time, Wefunder may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Wefunder also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and visitors commenting on Wefunder profile pages. Wefunder only discloses logged in user and visitor IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Wefunder’s websites choose to interact with Wefunder in ways that require Wefunder to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Wefunder gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our services to provide their full name and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Wefunder may be asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Wefunder collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Wefunder. Wefunder does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Wefunder may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Wefunder may monitor the most popular company profile sites. Wefunder may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Wefunder does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Wefunder discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Wefunder’s behalf or to provide services available at Wefunder’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Wefunder’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Wefunder will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Wefunder discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Wefunder believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Wefunder, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Wefunder website and have supplied your email address, Wefunder may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Wefunder and our products. We primarily use our blog and social media services to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Wefunder takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Wefunder uses cookies to help Wefunder identify and track visitors, their usage of Wefunder website, and their website access preferences. Wefunder visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Wefunder’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Wefunder’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Wefunder, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Wefunder goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Wefunder may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Wefunder and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Wefunder may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Wefunder’s sole discretion. Wefunder encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
